Haohua Su

415 W 120th St, New York, NY | (212) 518-6797 | shhsuhaohua520@gmail.com | https://github.com/suhh1123

SUMMARY

Seeking an internship software engineer position

Solid software engineer with strong programming, analyticl and communication skills. Has a wide range of software development related project experience, including full-stack web service development, recommendation system with Java, JavaScript and React, 5 years of programming experience with solid data structre and algorithms foundations

EDUCATION

Columbia University, Fu Foundation School of Engineering and Applied Science

New York, NY M.S. in Electrical Engineering Expected Dec 2022

Huazhong University of Science and Technology (HUST)

B.S. in Optoelectronic Information Science and Engineering, GPA: 3.61/4.0

Wuhan, CN Sep 2016 - Jun 2020

Programming Languages: MATLAB, Java, Python, C, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL

Techniques: RESTful services, AWS, Android Development, MySQL, Microservices, Kubernetes

Frameworks: Spring Boot, Spring MVC, Spring Security, Spring WebFlow, Spring Cloud, Django, Hibernate, React

EXPERIENCE

UAV Delivery Management System - TuFastly

Nov 2020 - Dec 2020

- Pulled off a management system for a logistics company that uses robots and drones to deliver packages, featured with user sign-up and login, robot or drone selection, route and price preview and order placement
- Led a team of 5 members to manage back-end development, and be responsible for route preview and route optimization feature, assisted database design and connected members from front end to make sure features deliver
- Organized teamwork, members communication and tasks synchronization with the help of JIRA, Git and Slack

Spring based Shopping System

Sep 2020 - Oct 2020

- Employed Spring MVC to support item search, listing and other business logics, database operations in application, centralize and manage object construction with Dependency Injection
- Integrated security workflow via in-memory and IDBC authentication provided by Spring Security
- Utilized Hibernate to simplify database operations
- Streamlined check-out process with Spring Web Flow

React JS based Starlink Trajectory Visualization

Sep 2020 - Oct 2020

- Developed a visualization dashboard leveraging ReactJS, AntD and React Simple Map to track satellites based on predicted coordinates data within a time span achieved from N2YO API
- Provided a search form for users entering longitude, latitude, altitude, and radius information to pinpoint satellites in a certain range
- Displayed information for those satellites in search range for users to select
- Animated selected satellites paths on a world map and recorded track with smooth curves

AWS based Web Service Development – Job Recommendation

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020

- Created a system deployed in EC2 with 3 Java servlets with RESTful APIs to handle HTTP requests and responses
- Fetched positions data from Github Job API and stored favorite records in MySQL database on Amazon RDS
- Capitalized on MonkeyLearn API to extract keywords from descriptions of positions
- Designed a content-based recommendation algorithm to implement job recommendation
- Developed an web page for user interaction (search and favor positions) with HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Image Intensification in Hybrid Space Based on MATLAB

Sep 2019 - Jun 2020

- Built a GUI containing 5 types of noise and 11 types of filter model to visualize noise impact on images and filter effect
- Proposed an improved histogram equalization algorithm IPDCLHE and dramatically improved brightness preservation performance and unnatural enhancement of DCLHE
- Compared IPDCLHE performance with 9 types of mature histogram equalization algorithms such as QDHE, BHEPL in terms of 7 objective indicators such as GMSD, AMBE, Information Entropy

LEADERSHIP

Head of International Exchange Department, Students' Union of HUST

May 2018 - May 2019

- Organized over 20 information sessions including college admission, company recruitment, and lectures
- Held over 15 original activities, such as International Student Orientation and Cultural Exchange Activity
- Received exchange delegations and foreign college visitors from over 20 countries